==========conll03_train==========
total_num_sentences: 14040
total_num_tokens: 203617
total_num_labels: 203617
total_num_golds: 23219
total_num_nonentity: 180398
labels: ['LOC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'PER']
gold_length_distribution: {'1': 14575, '2': 7361, '3': 903, '4': 250, '5': 82, '6': 25, '7': 18, '8': 2, '9': 0, '10': 3, 'extra': 0}

==========conll03_train_20.txt==========
total_num_sentences: 2808
total_num_tokens: 40793
total_num_labels: 40793
total_num_golds: 4601
total_num_nonentity: 36192
labels: ['LOC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'PER']
gold_length_distribution: {'1': 2938, '2': 1400, '3': 188, '4': 56, '5': 12, '6': 3, '7': 3, '8': 1, '9': 0, '10': 0, 'extra': 0}

==========conll03_train_40.txt==========
total_num_sentences: 5616
total_num_tokens: 82098
total_num_labels: 82098
total_num_golds: 9320
total_num_nonentity: 72778
labels: ['LOC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'PER']
gold_length_distribution: {'1': 5879, '2': 2921, '3': 359, '4': 106, '5': 37, '6': 9, '7': 6, '8': 0, '9': 0, '10': 3, 'extra': 0}

==========conll03_train_60.txt==========
total_num_sentences: 8424
total_num_tokens: 122259
total_num_labels: 122259
total_num_golds: 13906
total_num_nonentity: 108353
labels: ['LOC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'PER']
gold_length_distribution: {'1': 8670, '2': 4465, '3': 563, '4': 138, '5': 46, '6': 10, '7': 12, '8': 0, '9': 0, '10': 2, 'extra': 0}

==========conll03_train_80.txt==========
total_num_sentences: 11232
total_num_tokens: 162699
total_num_labels: 162699
total_num_golds: 18603
total_num_nonentity: 144096
labels: ['LOC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'PER']
gold_length_distribution: {'1': 11642, '2': 5922, '3': 723, '4': 214, '5': 64, '6': 22, '7': 13, '8': 0, '9': 0, '10': 3, 'extra': 0}

==========conll03_devel==========
total_num_sentences: 3249
total_num_tokens: 51358
total_num_labels: 51358
total_num_golds: 5860
total_num_nonentity: 45498
labels: ['LOC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'PER']
gold_length_distribution: {'1': 3689, '2': 1853, '3': 205, '4': 83, '5': 19, '6': 3, '7': 6, '8': 0, '9': 0, '10': 2, 'extra': 0}

==========conll03_devel_20.txt==========
total_num_sentences: 650
total_num_tokens: 10405
total_num_labels: 10405
total_num_golds: 1207
total_num_nonentity: 9198
labels: ['LOC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'PER']
gold_length_distribution: {'1': 750, '2': 398, '3': 39, '4': 16, '5': 2, '6': 1, '7': 1, '8': 0, '9': 0, '10': 0, 'extra': 0}

==========conll03_devel_40.txt==========
total_num_sentences: 1300
total_num_tokens: 19791
total_num_labels: 19791
total_num_golds: 2302
total_num_nonentity: 17489
labels: ['LOC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'PER']
gold_length_distribution: {'1': 1443, '2': 726, '3': 83, '4': 39, '5': 4, '6': 2, '7': 5, '8': 0, '9': 0, '10': 0, 'extra': 0}

==========conll03_devel_60.txt==========
total_num_sentences: 1949
total_num_tokens: 30849
total_num_labels: 30849
total_num_golds: 3535
total_num_nonentity: 27314
labels: ['LOC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'PER']
gold_length_distribution: {'1': 2218, '2': 1119, '3': 131, '4': 51, '5': 12, '6': 1, '7': 2, '8': 0, '9': 0, '10': 1, 'extra': 0}

==========conll03_devel_80.txt==========
total_num_sentences: 2599
total_num_tokens: 40986
total_num_labels: 40986
total_num_golds: 4755
total_num_nonentity: 36231
labels: ['LOC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'PER']
gold_length_distribution: {'1': 3002, '2': 1492, '3': 166, '4': 71, '5': 16, '6': 2, '7': 5, '8': 0, '9': 0, '10': 1, 'extra': 0}

==========conll04_train==========
total_num_sentences: 922
total_num_tokens: 26525
total_num_labels: 26525
total_num_golds: 3315
total_num_nonentity: 23210
labels: ['LOC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'PER']
gold_length_distribution: {'1': 1480, '2': 1110, '3': 486, '4': 181, '5': 35, '6': 16, '7': 4, '8': 0, '9': 1, '10': 0, 'extra': 2}

==========conll04_train_20.txt==========
total_num_sentences: 184
total_num_tokens: 5623
total_num_labels: 5623
total_num_golds: 672
total_num_nonentity: 4951
labels: ['LOC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'PER']
gold_length_distribution: {'1': 299, '2': 219, '3': 116, '4': 30, '5': 6, '6': 1, '7': 1, '8': 0, '9': 0, '10': 0, 'extra': 0}

==========conll04_train_40.txt==========
total_num_sentences: 369
total_num_tokens: 10318
total_num_labels: 10318
total_num_golds: 1320
total_num_nonentity: 8998
labels: ['LOC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'PER']
gold_length_distribution: {'1': 575, '2': 431, '3': 210, '4': 82, '5': 12, '6': 6, '7': 2, '8': 0, '9': 1, '10': 0, 'extra': 1}

==========conll04_train_60.txt==========
total_num_sentences: 553
total_num_tokens: 15657
total_num_labels: 15657
total_num_golds: 1980
total_num_nonentity: 13677
labels: ['LOC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'PER']
gold_length_distribution: {'1': 896, '2': 649, '3': 294, '4': 104, '5': 24, '6': 9, '7': 2, '8': 0, '9': 1, '10': 0, 'extra': 1}

==========conll04_train_80.txt==========
total_num_sentences: 738
total_num_tokens: 21457
total_num_labels: 21457
total_num_golds: 2704
total_num_nonentity: 18753
labels: ['LOC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'PER']
gold_length_distribution: {'1': 1215, '2': 898, '3': 404, '4': 143, '5': 28, '6': 11, '7': 4, '8': 0, '9': 0, '10': 0, 'extra': 1}

==========conll04_devel==========
total_num_sentences: 231
total_num_tokens: 6993
total_num_labels: 6993
total_num_golds: 875
total_num_nonentity: 6118
labels: ['LOC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'PER']
gold_length_distribution: {'1': 416, '2': 275, '3': 129, '4': 37, '5': 12, '6': 1, '7': 4, '8': 0, '9': 1, '10': 0, 'extra': 0}

==========conll04_devel_20.txt==========
total_num_sentences: 46
total_num_tokens: 1340
total_num_labels: 1340
total_num_golds: 164
total_num_nonentity: 1176
labels: ['LOC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'PER']
gold_length_distribution: {'1': 75, '2': 54, '3': 21, '4': 8, '5': 4, '6': 0, '7': 2, '8': 0, '9': 0, '10': 0, 'extra': 0}

==========conll04_devel_40.txt==========
total_num_sentences: 92
total_num_tokens: 2801
total_num_labels: 2801
total_num_golds: 360
total_num_nonentity: 2441
labels: ['LOC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'PER']
gold_length_distribution: {'1': 179, '2': 115, '3': 44, '4': 13, '5': 6, '6': 1, '7': 2, '8': 0, '9': 0, '10': 0, 'extra': 0}

==========conll04_devel_60.txt==========
total_num_sentences: 139
total_num_tokens: 4121
total_num_labels: 4121
total_num_golds: 511
total_num_nonentity: 3610
labels: ['LOC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'PER']
gold_length_distribution: {'1': 221, '2': 179, '3': 78, '4': 20, '5': 8, '6': 1, '7': 3, '8': 0, '9': 1, '10': 0, 'extra': 0}

==========conll04_devel_80.txt==========
total_num_sentences: 185
total_num_tokens: 5552
total_num_labels: 5552
total_num_golds: 695
total_num_nonentity: 4857
labels: ['LOC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'PER']
gold_length_distribution: {'1': 327, '2': 224, '3': 101, '4': 30, '5': 9, '6': 1, '7': 3, '8': 0, '9': 0, '10': 0, 'extra': 0}